Railroad Case Files 5014
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board between Railway Employees Dept., AFL and New York Central Lines. U.S. Board of Mediation C-351 Vol. 1, 2, 13-16, 23-25. 11/28-1/29. (Box 6)
  - Statement Showing Tractive Power of Locomotives in Freight Service Years 1917, 1923, and 1926, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Freight Services: Southeastern Railroads, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Capital Expenditures: Southeastern Railroads, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, U.S. Board of Mediation, File C-193 Arb., 1927 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    Between Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen vs. Certain Railroads in Southeastern Territory
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, U.S. Board of Mediation, File C-193 Arb., 1927 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, U.S. Board of Mediation, File C-193 Arb., 1927 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, U.S. Board of Mediation, File C-193 Arb., 1927 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, U.S. Board of Mediation, File C-193 Arb., 1927 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, U.S. Board of Mediation, File C-193 Arb., 1927 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, U.S. Board of Mediation, File C-193 Arb., 1927 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, U.S. Board of Mediation, File C-193 Arb., 1927 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, U.S. Board of Mediation, File C-193 Arb., 1927 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, U.S. Board of Mediation, File C-193 Arb., 1927 (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Between BLF&E vs. Certain Railroads in Southeastern Territory. U.S. Board of Mediation. File C-193 Arb. 10 volumes, plus exhibits, 1927. (Box 7)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 16, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Between Certain Western Railroads and The Order of Railway Conductors and The Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 15, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 14, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 13, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 12, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 11, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 10, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 9, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 8, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 7, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 6, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 5, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 4, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 3, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 2, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume No. 1, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board Between Certain Western Railroads and ORC and BRT. 9/29/28. 16 volumes. (Box 8)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volumes 27 and 28, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Between the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen vs. Certain Western Railroads; U.S. Boards of Mediation File C-266 Arb.
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volumes 25 and 26, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volumes 23 and 24, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volumes 21 and 22, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volumes 19 and 20, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volumes 17 and 18, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volumes 15 and 16, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volumes 13 and 14, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volumes 11 and 12, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volumes 9 and 10, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volumes 7 and 8, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volumes 5 and 6, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume 4, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volumes 2 and 3, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume 1, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Between BLF&E vs. Certain Western Railroads, U.S. Board of Mediation, File C-266, Arb. 1927, volumes 1-28. (Box 9)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volumes 29 and 30, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volumes 31 and 32, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volumes 33 and 34, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volumes 35 and 36, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volumes 37 and 38, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volumes 39 and 40, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volumes 41 and 42, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume 43, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volumes 44 and 45, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volumes 46 and 47, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume 48 and 49, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volumes 50 and 51, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volumes 52 and 53, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume 54, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume 55, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volumes 56 and 57, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Between BLF&E vs. Certain Western Railroads, U.S. Board of Mediation, File C-266, Arb. 1927, volumes 1-28. (Box 10)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Report and Award of Arbitrators, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Between the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers and Certain Southeastern Railroads; U.S. Boards of Mediation File C-275 Arb.
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Exhibits and Evidence Files 1 through 21, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume 13, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume 12, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume 11, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume 10, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume 9, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume 8, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume 7, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume 6, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume 5, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume 4, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume 3, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume 2, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume 1, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Between BLE and Certain Southeastern Railroads, U.S. Board of Mediation File C-275 Arb., 1/3/28 plus exhibits. (Box 11)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume 5, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Between Railroads represented by Eastern, Western, and Southeastern Carriers' Conference Committees and Their Employees represented by the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen; Emergency Board No. 110 Case A-4854
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume 3, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Report to the President by the Emergency Board, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Appointed by Executive Order 10615, dated June 17, 1955, pursuant to Section 10 of The Railway Labor Act, as amended
  - Before the Emergency Board: Brief on Behalf of the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Between certain Railroads represented by Eastern, Western, and Southeastern Carriers' Conference Committees and certain of their Employees represented by the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen; Emergency Board No. 110 Case A-4854
  - Report to the President by Emergency Board No. 110, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume 2, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume 12, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume 11, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume 9, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume 8, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume 7, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume 1, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume 13, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume 14, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume 4, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume 6, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume 15, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume 10, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Labor Dispute between Railroad Carriers and Four Operating Railroad Brotherhoods: Hearings before the Committee on Labor and Public Welfare, United States Senate, Eighty-Second Congress, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    First Session on Labor Dispute between Railroad Carriers and Four Operating Railroad Brotherhoods
- Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board #110, Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carrier's Conference Committee and BLF&E, Case A-4854, 1955, Volumes 1-2 plus briefs and exhibits. (Box 12)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 1, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Between the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen and Order of Railway Conductors, vs. Certain Western Railroads; US Board of Mediation File C-188 Arb.
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 2, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 3, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 4, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 5, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 6, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 7, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 8, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 9, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 10, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 11, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 12, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 13, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 14, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 15, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 16, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 17, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 18, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 19, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 20, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 21, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 22, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 23, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 24, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 25, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 26, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 27, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 28, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 29, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 30, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board Volume 31, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board. ORC and BRT vs. Certain Western Railroads, File C-188 Arb., 1927- Volumes 1-31. (Box 13)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume 38, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Between the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen and Order of Railway Conductors vs. Certain Western Railroads; US Board of Mediation File C-188 Arb.
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume 37, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume 36, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume 35, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume 34, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume 33, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the Arbitration Board, Volume 32, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Transcript of the Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume 8, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Appointed by the President of the United States to investigate and report upon certain differences between Texas & Pacific Railway Company and the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen & Enginemen, Order of Railway Conductors
  - Transcript of the Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume 7, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Transcript of the Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume 1, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Transcript of the Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume 2, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Transcript of the Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume 3, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Transcript of the Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume 4, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Transcript of the Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume 5, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Transcript of the Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume 6, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Volumes 32-38 of above case. (Box 14)
  - Transcript of the Proceedings of the Emergency Board, Volume 22, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Between Akron, Canton, and Youngstown Railroad and Other Carriers and the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, and Switchmen's Union of North America
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the National Mediation Board, Emergency Board No. 164, Volume 3, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Carriers represented by National Railway Labor Conference and the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the National Mediation Board, Emergency Board No. 164, Volume 4, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the National Mediation Board, Emergency Board No. 164, Volume 5, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the National Mediation Board, Emergency Board No. 164, Volume 6, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the National Mediation Board, Emergency Board No. 164, Volume 9, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the National Mediation Board, Emergency Board No. 164, Volume 8, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Transcript of Proceedings of the National Mediation Board, Emergency Board No. 164, Volume 7, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Stenographer's Minutes before the Interstate Commerce Commission, Docket No. 20247 et seq., 1928 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Public Utilities Commission of the State of Ohio vs. The Pennsylvania Railroad
  - Stenographer's Minutes before the Interstate Commerce Commission, Docket No. 20247 and 20746, 1928 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Stenographer's Minutes before the Interstate Commerce Commission Docket, No. 24049, 1936 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    A. Johnston, Grand Chief Engineer of the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, et al. vs. Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railway Company, et al.
  - (minutes) (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Excerpts from Testimony: Advanced Rate Case. Ex Parte 74, Vol. 1-A Increased Rates, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    From the Association of Railway Executives, for release in newspapers of May 5, 1920
  - Excerpts from Testimony: Advanced Rate Case. Ex Parte 74, Vol. 2, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    "In the matter of applications of carriers in Official, Southern, and Western Classification Territories for authority to increase rates"
  - Excerpts from Testimony: Advanced Rate Case. Ex Parte 74, Vol. 3, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Excerpts from Testimony: Advanced Rate Case. Ex Parte 74, Vol. 5, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Excerpts from Testimony: Advanced Rate Case. Ex Parte 74, Vol. 4, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Excerpts from Testimony: Advanced Rate Case. Ex Parte 74, Vol. 7, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Excerpts from Testimony: Advanced Rate Case. Ex Parte 74, Vol. 6, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Excerpts from Testimony: Advanced Rate Case. Ex Parte 74, Vol. 8, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Excerpts from Testimony: Advanced Rate Case. Ex Parte 74, Vol. 9, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Excerpts from Testimony: Advanced Rate Case. Ex Parte 74, Vol. 10, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Excerpts from Testimony: Advanced Rate Case. Ex Parte 74, Vol. 11, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Excerpts from Testimony: Advanced Rate Case. Ex Parte 74, Vol. 12, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Excerpts from Testimony: Advanced Rate Case. Ex Parte 74, Vol. 13, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Excerpts from Testimony: Advanced Rate Case. Ex Parte 74, Vol. 15, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Excerpts from Testimony: Advanced Rate Case. Ex Parte 74, Vol. 1, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission Finance Docket No. 21478 Vol. 1, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    Great Northern Pacific & Burlington Lines: Merger, etc.
  - Interstate Commerce Commission Finance Docket No. 21478 Vol. 2, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Before the Interstate Commerce Commission Finance Docket No. 23178, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    In the matter of the Application for a Merger Between the Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company and the Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company
  - Post-War Traffic Levels, 1944 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    Published by the Interstate Commerce Commission Bureau of Transport Economics and Statistics
  - Stenographer's Minutes Docket No. 20247 et seq. before the Interstate Commerce Commission, 1928 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Letter from Emery R. Hayhurst to Timothy Shea, 1936 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    Hayhurst is a Consulting Industrial Hygienist and Shea is Asst. President of the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen & Enginemen; letter dated June 18, 1936
  - Testimony of F.W. Sargent before the Interstate Commerce Commission, Docket No. 17000, 1925 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    Rate Structure Investigation, Ex Parte 87, Revenues in Western District
- Reporter's Minutes, Docket No. 24049 before the Interstate Commerce Commission, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Official Stenographer's Minutes, Docket No. Ex Parte 38 before the International Commerce Commission, 1929 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  In the matter of rules and instructions for the inspection and testing of steam locomotives and tenders in accordance with the act of February 17, 1911, as amended. Petition of the Boston & Maine Railroad Company for exemption of certain of its steam.
- Rules Governing the Classification of Railroad Employees and Reports of their Service and Compensation, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Hearings before a Subcommittee of the Committee on Interstate Commerce, United States Senate, 74th Congress, First Session on S. 59, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Hearings before a Subcommittee of the Committee on Interstate Commerce, United States Senate, 68th Congress, First Session on S. 2646, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Hearings before the Committee on Interstate Commerce, United States Senate, 69th Congress, First Session on S. 2306, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Interstate Commerce Commission, No. 12964, 1929 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  Consolidation of Railroads in the matter of consolidation of the railway properties of the United States into a limited number of systems
- Hearings before the Committee on Interstate Commerce United States Senate, 69th Congress, First Session on S. 2306, Part 2, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- A Statistical Analysis of Carriers' Monthly Hours of Service Reports: 1936 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- A Statistical Analysis of Carriers' Monthly Hours of Service Reports: 1935 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- A Statistical Analysis of Carriers' Monthly Hours of Service Reports: 1939 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- A Statistical Analysis of Carriers' Monthly Hours of Service Reports: 1938 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- A Statistical Analysis of Carriers' Monthly Hours of Service Reports: 1913 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- A Statistical Analysis of Carriers' Monthly Hours of Service Reports: 1929 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- A Statistical Analysis of Carriers' Monthly Hours of Service Reports: 1926 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- A Statistical Analysis of Carriers' Monthly Hours of Service Reports: 1914 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- A Statistical Analysis of Carriers' Monthly Hours of Service Reports: 1915 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- A Statistical Analysis of Carriers' Monthly Hours of Service Reports: 1921 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- A Statistical Analysis of Carriers' Monthly Hours of Service Reports: 1917 (Box 15, Folder 19)